Guide to the Donald Kennedy Personal Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Donald Kennedy personal papers
1975-2007
SC0708
Kennedy, Donald, 1931-
15.5 Linear feet
This collection contains his speech files dating from 1975 to 2007; these include Stanford events, commencements at other universities, conferences, government testimony, memorials, and others. There is also an unprocessed accession (2003-003) which includes his personal copies of congressional hearings while serving as FDA Commissioner.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
Access: Please consult the University Archivist for access to the unprocessed materials.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Kennedy, holder of three degrees from Harvard, joined Stanford's biology faculty in 1960; while on leave from 1977 to 1979 he served in Washington, D.C., as commissioner of the Food and Drug Administration. Kennedy was Stanford's eighth president, serving from 1980 to 1992. Prior to taking office he was vice president and provost under his predecessor Richard W. Lyman. During his presidency, Stanford celebrated its centennial and its full emergence as a world-class university. Kennedy was at the forefront of the university's student public service initiative and efforts to renew faculty commitment to teaching. His term in office also included the university's disagreement with the federal government over reimbursement for the indirect costs of research.
Description of the Collection
This collection contains his speech files dating from 1975 to 2007; these include Stanford events, commencements at other universities, conferences, government testimony, memorials, and others. There is also an unprocessed accession (2003-003) which includes his personal copies of congressional hearings while serving as FDA Commissioner.
Access Terms
Kennedy, Donald, 1931-; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2003-003
  - DK's personal copies of congressional hearings while serving as FDA Commissioner (Box 1)
  - DK's personal copies of congressional hearings while serving as FDA Commissioner (Box 2)
  - Books (Box 3)
  - Books (Box 4)
  - Books (Box 5)
  - Ice Cream, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Laetrile, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Acrylonitrile, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Darvon, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Lead, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Lead Acetate, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Liquid Proton, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Nitrite, 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Saccharin, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sodium Valproate, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Alpha-Fetoprotein, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Phenformin, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Frank Morrell, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - H. Bruce Franklin 1/5, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - H. Bruce Franklin 2/5, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - H. Bruce Franklin 3/5, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - H. Bruce Franklin 4/5, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - H. Bruce Franklin 5/5, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - SIDS + DTP Vaccine, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - A Proposed FDA Program to Reduce Unnecessary Patient Exposure From Diagnostic X Rays: Cost Containment Considerations, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - PMS Briefing to the Commissioner Ionizing Radiation--Products and Devices Ionizing Radiation--Use Control, 28265 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - FDA Related Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - FDA Related Manuscripts, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - FDA Consumer Magazine Article, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - FDA--Info Only, 1978-1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - OSTP--Recombinant DNA--Background, Etc. 1/2, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - OSTP--Recombinant DNA--Background, Etc. 2/2, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Professional Appointments, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Professional Appointments, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Professional Appointments, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Professional Appointments, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cassette: Donald Kennedy, "New Tests for SCIENCE", 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "New threat to research funds", 29990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Asahi Shimbun, Tokyo, 31745 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - The Politics of Preventive Health by Donald Kennedy, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Cleaning up the Smog Act (DK Info), 29618 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Promise of Fact (DK info), 29707 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Recommendations and Correspondence involving Donald Kennedy, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Brochure: How can we look so rich, yet feel so poor?, 31487 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Forty-First Meeting of the Trustees of Midwest Research Institute, 31554 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Basic Research in the Universities: How Much Utility?, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Addreses and Proceedings--The Idea of Education: Rediscovery of Purpose in a Brave New World, 4/12-13/1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "Business, Science and the Universities", 29726 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Health Affairs Fall 1983 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Academy News--"Stanford's President Takes a Long-Range look", 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Brandeis University: Inauguration of Evelyn Erika Handler`, 30608 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Technology Review, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Educating for the Twenty-First Century, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Scroll by TRL, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Bay Area Business (DK info), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Mobius, A Journal for Continuing Education Professional in Health Sciences, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The Stanford Magazine Winter 1982 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Loose Articles, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 1980 Articles (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Equal Opportunity Forum Stanford in Review, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Language and the Brain, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - FDA Related Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Chronological files, 1993-1995 (Box 8)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-139
  - Human Biology & Public Policy University Seminar 11/21/75 (#AA) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clockwork Versus Value – Harvard Class Day 5/25/79 (#1A) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Executive Program Bishop Auditorium August 1, 1979 2-3:15pm (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Jackson Laboratory's 1979 Anniversary Speaker Series Bar Harbor, Maine August 8-12, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - WIERSMA Memorial Service 10/2/79 (#4) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - WIERSMA Memorial Remarks 10/2/79 and General Biology Seminar – Cal Tech 10/2/79 (#5) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - SF Major Gifts Committee 10/23/79 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Homeowners Assn. Talk 11/14/79 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Management Development Group November 16, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Industrial Affiliates Symposia Science, Regulation, and Risk Aversion December 3, 1979 (Banquet) Faculty Club (#11) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Food and Drug Law Institute 30th Anniversary Annual Banquet Washington, D.C. December 11, 1979 (#12) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Forsythe Dedication 1/14/80 (#13) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pills & the Public Purse 1/30/80 (#14A) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pills and the Public Purse Foreword 1/30/80 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Drug and Device Regulation: The Government's Role Snowmass January 14-18, 1980 (#15) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - DK's Fundraising Trip to NY 2/4-7/80 (#16) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Swopsi Lecture: A Look at Health Regulation: The Food Safety Laws 2/7/80 (#17) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Frontiers of Science Series University of Utah Salt Lake City, Utah February 15-17, 1980 (#18) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Committee for Art Board of Governors 2/19/80 (#19) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Libraries Group 2/22/80 (#20) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Commonwealth Club S.F. 2/29/80 (#21) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Commonwealth Club (#21) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Science and Health Regulation Journal of Dental Education 3/80 (#22) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Politics of Health Western Assn. of Venture Capitalists 3/11/80 (#23) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - PEP Dedication 9/5/80 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Medical School 20th Anniversary Symposium Dinner 3/27/80 (#24) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - California Academy of Medicine San Francisco St. Francis Hotel Saturday, March 29, 1980 (#25) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Regulation: Both Sides of the Barrier April, 1980 (#26) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Regulation: Both Sides of the Barrier 4/80 (#26) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Meetings, Donor P.R. Washington/Boston/Chicago/New York April 20-26, 1980 (#27) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - GSB Advisory Council May 1, 1980 (#28) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Wilson Riles introduction Univ. Fellows, June, 1980 (#29) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Drug Regulation 6/4/80 (#30) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Class Day Plaque-laying June 14, 1980 (#31) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Class Day Plaque Laying 6/14/80 (#31) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Western Economic Association (WEA) Sheraton Harbor Island Hotel San Diego June 15-19, 1980 Regulation and the Quality of Life (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Regulation and the Universities (#33) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Regulation and the Universities Science, June 16, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Nero or Nanny: The Dilemma of Health Regulation (#33A) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Nero or Nanny: Dilemma of Health Reg (#33A) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Evolution of Health Regulation (#33B) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - AMA version Regulation and Medicine 76th Congress on Medical Education Chicago 4-1-80 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Dedication Margaret Jacks Hall June 20, 1980 (#34) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Regulation and the Health Profession Mobius 7/80 (Barbara Riddle) (#35) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Albers Wall Dedication 8/1/80 (#37) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Speech to House Staff Physicians July 11, 1980 (draft) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Albers Wall Dedication 8/1/80 (#37) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Board Presentation on Hospital Modernization 8/28/80 (#37A) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Fundraising in the 80s 8/15/80 (#37B) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - PEP Dedication (#38) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Gold Spike Awards 9/12/80 Maples Pavilion (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Parents Day Convocation 9/25/80 (#40) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Welcome to Transfers 9/26/80 (#41) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Welcome to Freshmen Memorial Auditorium 9/80 (#41A) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Graduate Student Convocation 1980-81 (#41B) (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Talk to Academic Council 10/3/80 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Messenger Lecture I Health Science and Regulation The Politics of Prevention 10/7/80 (#43) (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - The Politics of Prevention 10/7/80 (#43) (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Messenger Lectures Cornell University, Ithaca, NY (#43) (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Messenger Lecture II The Assessment and Management of Risk 10/8/80 (#44) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - The Assessment & Management of Risk 10/8/80 (#44) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Messenger Lecture III Where Does Science Leave Off, and Reg… 10/8/80 (#45) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Where Does Science Leave Off? 10/8/80 (#45) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Introduction for Hamburg Symposium 10/18/80 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - General Alumni Talk 11/7/80 (#48) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Academic Senate Meeting 11/13/80 (#49) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, Cornell, Indiana, Stanford Some Connections; Jordan Centennial Lecture 12/4/80 (#50) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, Cornell, Indiana, Stanford: Some Connections 12/4/80 (#50) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Health Research: Can Utility and Quality Co-Exist? Pennsylvania 12/6/80 (#51) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Palo Alto City Council 12/89 (#51A) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - FDA and Congress 1/6/81 (#52) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Academic Council 12/31/80 (#53) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Winter Quarter Academic Council 1/9/81 (non-academic staff) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Crow Associates 1/29/81 (#55) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The University and Industry 2/5/81 (Talk to Bechtel Wives) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Tuition Tax Credits Washington Post Op-Ed Page 3/81 (#57) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Alumni Conference L.A. 3/5/81 (#58) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Speech to Medical Staff 3/17/81 (#59) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The University and Industry Colorado Council of Deans Ass. Am. Med. Colleges 3/30-31/81 (#60) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Report to Academic Council Graduate Financial Aid 4/3/81 (#61) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Charter Day Berkeley 4/9/81 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The University and Industry (given at AAU) 4/13/81 (#63) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Time Dinner NYC 4/13/81 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Darwin Lecture – Humanities 4/29/81 (#65) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Darwin lecture 4/29/81 (#65) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Reception Sheraton Palace, San Francisco 4/29/81 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bing Retirement Dinner 5/11/81 Sheraton Palace, San Francisco (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Conference on Good Teaching 5/11-12/81 School of Education, Stanford (#68) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Committee for Corporate Support of Private Universities NYC 5/20/81 (#69) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Athletic Awards Banquet 5/13/81 (#69A) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Hospital Awards Banquet Hyatt, Palo Alto 5/29/81 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - GSB Alumni Talk 5/81 (#70A) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Management Development Group 6/2/81 (#71) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Address 1981 Stanford 6/14/81 (#72) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Northern California Grantmakers Meeting Stanford 6/18/81 (#73) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Senate – Tax Incentives – R&D Washington, D.C. "Dole" 5/21/81 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - House of Representatives, Gore Committee on Science & Technology "Commercializing…" 6/8/81 (#75) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Stanford Engineering Executives Program 7/2/81 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Psoriasis Conference Medical Center Stanford 7/12/81 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Executive Program in the Humanities Welcome to Participants 7/13/81 (#78) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Mills College Greeting on Behalf of private institutions 9/17/81 (#79) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Mills College Greeting Private Inst. 9/17/81 (#79) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Order and Disorder Symposium 9/16/81 (#80) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Welcome to RAs 9/20/81 (#81) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Greetings to Medical Students 9/21/81 (#82) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Freshman Orientation 9/24/81 (#83) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Parents Day Convocation 9/24/81 (#83) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Inaugural Address, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Welcome to Transfers 9/24/81 (#83) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Castilleja Anniversary Greeting 9/17/81 (#84) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Science Editorial 1982 (#85) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Academic Council Planning in the University 19/2/81 (#87) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Heart Disease Prevention Program 19/7/81 (#88) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Library Dedication Introduction of Lyman 10/9/81 (#89) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sterling Quad Groundbreaking 10/12/81 (#90) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - United Way Pillars Luncheon 10/15/81 (#91) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Blood Center Dedication 10/16/81 (#92) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Richard Atkinson Inauguration UCSD 10/21/81 (#93) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Talk 10/28/81 (#94) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges Washington DC 11/2/81 (#95) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Regulation and Health 11/11/81 (#95B) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sandra Day O'Connor Reception Washington, DC 11/17/81 (#96) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Advancing Knowledge Carnegie Fdn. 75th Anniversary Colloquium 11/23/81 (#97) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Winter Quarter Academic Council on Taking Positions 1/8/82 (#98) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - The State of the University Presidential Reception – Honolulu 1/82 (#99) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hearing on HR 4326 Small Business Innovation Development Act 1/27/82 (#100) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Testimony – House of Reps Ways & Means "Impact of Admin Budget Cuts" 1/18/82 (#100A) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Palo Alto City Council Meeting 3/15/82 (#101) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Science in the Dock The Washington Post 2/4/82 (#102) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - MIT Health Research and Policy Institute 3/4/82 (#103) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - LA Alumni Conference Talk 3/7/82 (#104) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Message for Stanford Quad 3/12/82 (#105) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Pajaro Dunes Conference 3/25-27/82 (#106) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Tanner Lecture Welcome 3/31/82 (#107) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Spring Quarter Academic Council 4/9/82 (#108) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Undergraduate Education 4/82 (#108) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Management Development Program Introduction of Richard W. Lyman 4/16/82 (#109) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Consortium for Health Research & Policy 4/17/82 (#110) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Law School Board of Visitors 4/22/82 (#110A) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Long-Term Biological Consequences of Nuclear War (#174) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - SWOPSI Lecture: Univ., Industries, and Grad. Ed.: What's at Stake 4/26/82 (#11) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Science: The Government, Secrecy, and Univ. Research 4/23/82 (#112) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Senior Athletes Dinner 5/11/82 (#113) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Senior Athletes Dinner 5/11/82 (#113) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Senior Athletes Dinner (#113) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - "Tall Tree Awards" Dinner Hyatt, Palo Alto 6/2/82 (#114) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Commencement Talk 6/13/82 (#115) (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Celebrate Diversity Draft 4/82 (#116) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - GSB-MDP Executive Program July 1982 (#117) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - American Council on Germany 8/6/82 (#119) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Palo Alto City Council Meeting 8/9/82 (#120) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - The University & Government Summer Alumni College/F.C. 8/3/82 (#121) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Summer Convocation – U of Michigan Ann Arbor, Mich 8/23/82 (#122) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - John Gardner Dinner Remarks 9/13/92 (#123) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Stanford Un. Library Assoc. Before Darwin, and After Sept. 19, 1982 (#124) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Before Darwin and After 9/19/82 (#124) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Senate: USW Strike Issues Sept. 30, 1982 and Oct. 14, 1982 (#125) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Orientation Week, 1982 Parents Day Conv., Freshman Orient (#126) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Univ. of Oregon Fall Convocation On Science and ‘Culture' Oct. 4, 1982 (#127) (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - American Council Fall Quarter Rept Convocation 10/4/82 (#128) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - The Social Sponsorship of Innovation, October 21, 1982 (#129) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Harvard Biological Labs 50th Ann. 10/22/82 (#130) (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Higher Ed: Pub & Private Foothill-DeAnza 25th Anniversary 10/29/82 (#131) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bohemian Club – Big Game Nite Nov, 1982 (#132) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Managing in Government and the Academy" 12/6/82 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Terman Memorial (Frederick) 1/4/83 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rept. To Senate 1/6/83 (#136) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Intro of Seaga by DK Conference Internat'l Biz. 1/6/83 (#137) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kimball O.D. Lunch 1/18/83 (#138) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - "The Schools and Their Future: Who Will Lead?" Monterey 1/83 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Academic Council The Indirect Cost Problem 2/3/83 (#140) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Mastering Change in the Eighties YPO-Phoenix 2/18/83 (#141) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Faculty & Staff Benefits (Committee on) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lyman Portrait unveiling 3/8/83 (#143) Q.E.II. Toast 3/3/83 (#143A) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hearing on NSF Basic Research 3/9/83 (#144) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Retreat 3/24/83 (#145) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Spring Quarter Academic Council SSRL/LLL 4/1/83 (#146) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Palo Alto City Council Statement Stanford West 4/11/83 (#147) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Talks (#148) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - LA Alumni Conference 4/24/83 (#143A) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Zale Lecture – Intro of Gary Hart 4/22/83 (#149) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - The NIH Proposals on Indirect Cost 4/83 (#150) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Mission of the University 5/1/83 (#150A) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Clock Tower Dedication 5/10/83 (#151) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - "Origin of Man" poss. Institute (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - No. Calif. June 18 (#73) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Intro Clifford Geertz Camp Lecturer 5/16/83 (#154) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Majors Event (notes) 5/11/83 (#155) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Medical School Talk 5/83 (#156) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Molecular Genetics Symposium 5/83 (#157) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Conference on Entrepreneurship GSB 5/83 (#158) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Annual Editors Conference 5/83 (#159) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Testimony: Food Safety Legisl. 6/83 (#160) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Feigen Memorial Service 6/83 (#161) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Address 6/83 (#162) (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cost Containment, Quality & Access Merritt Peralta Med Center 7/20/83 (#163) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Federal Judges Talk University of Virginia 8/83 (#164) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Talk to Medical Staff 8/23/83 (#165) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pajaro Dunes Conference 8/83 nation's schools (#165A) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Orientation Week 1983 Freshman, Parents, Grads, Sophs, Shockley Statement 9/83 (#166) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Gold Spike Dinner Remarks 9/23/83 (#167) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Harvard Graduate Society 10/6/83 (#168) (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Prescription for Prevention Intro to PSR Symposium 10/7/83 (#169) (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - "New Universities, New Prospects" Brandeis 35th Ann., Handler Install. 10/9/83 (#170) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Fall Qrtr. Academic Council Convocation 10/12/83 (#171) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - L.A. Trustee Symposium 10/23/83 (#172) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Remarks to Faculty Senate 10/27/83 (#173) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Conference on the Long-Term Biological Consequences of Nuclear War 10/31/83 (#174) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - "Innovation & the University: Managing the Scientific Revolution" L.A. Rotary 11/4/83 (#175) (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Kennedy to Senate 12-8-83 (#176) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Testimony RE: Research University for President's Commission on Indus. 12/21/83 (#177) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Crow Associates 1/31/84 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - "The Great American Science Venture: Will It Survive?" Comstock Club 2/7/84 (#179) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Great American Science Venture 2/7/84 (#179) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Henry S. Kaplan Memorial Service 2/12/84 (#180) (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Statement on Soviet Jewry 2/84 (#181) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Senate – RRL 2/23/84 (#182) (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - You Can Make a Difference 2/25/84 (#183) (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - The Nervous System – How Is It Formed? 2/28/84 (#184) (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Statement: DK/BOT/RRL Relationship 3/15/84 (#185) (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Opening Remarks, Mitterrand 3/26/84 (#186) (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Stegner's Intro of Norman Maclean (#187A) (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - DK Reviews MacLean's "A River Runs Through It" (187B) (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Education in the Twenty-First Century April 28, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - L.A. Alumni Conf: Before Darwin & After 3/31/84 (#188A) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - MD program 5-1984 (#189) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Campus Conference (notes only) 5/12/84 (#189B) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Alumni Conference "New York Event" 4-1984 (#190) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Education in the Twenty-First Century "New York Event" 4-28-1984 (#190) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Western Association of Schools & Colleges Conference April 1984 S. Jose (#191) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - California Biomed. Research Association 4-30-1984 (#192) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 93rd Commencement Speech 6/17/84 (#193) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Dinner 7/18/84 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Testimony before the Committee of the Republican Platform 7-30-84 (#195) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Pief Panofksy's Retirement Dinner August 3, 1984 (#196) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Woods Hole Lecture "Gov't Policies & Cost of Living Doing Res." 8-17-1984 (#197) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sophomore Convocation Notes September 25, 1984 (#198) (Box 5, Folder 14)